Guide to the Radio TV Services Records, circa 1937-2012 UA.27.02.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Sound Recordings, 1960-1988 and undated
  - Reel-to-Reel Tapes, 1960-1975; undated; 4.2
    - Commencement Address: Dr. Merrimon Cunningham, Board of Trustees, 1963 (Box 5, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0009)
      Original identification number: B-23
    - Graduation Speech, undated (Box 5, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0010)
      Original identification number: B-24
    - Commencement: Dr. Calvin B. Hooper, Dr. Douglas Knight, June 1, 1964 (Box 5, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0011)
      Original identification number: B-30
    - Dr. Arthur Larson, June 11, 1964 (Box 5, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0012)
      Original identification number: B-39
    - News Conference: Phytotron Announcement, June 29, 1964; 1 sound reel: 5 inch, 1/4 inch. (Box 5, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0013)
      Original identification number: B-44
    - Library: Dan McGrath, Curator, Rare Books Room, July 22, 1964 (Box 5, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0014)
      Original identification number: B-47
    - Oceanography: Dr. Menzies on oceanographic research, undated (Box 5, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0015)
      Original identification number: B-49
    - R. T. Cole: J. B. Duke Profs, July 22, 1964 (Box 5, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0016)
      Original identification number: B-76
    - Founder's Day: Dr. Knight's Speech, Dec. 10, 1962 (Box 5, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0017)
      Original identification number: B-83-1
    - Founder's Day: Dr. Knight's Speech, Dec. 10, 1962 (Box 5, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0018)
      Original identification number: B-83-2
    - Founder's Day: Dr. Knight's Speech, Dec. 10, 1962 (Box 5, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0019)
      Original identification number: B-83-3
    - Commonwealth Interview, Commonwealth Studies Center: Dr. Robert Wilson, Dec. 10, 1962 (Box 5, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0020)
      Original identification number: B-85
    - Convocation: Dr. Knight's Speech, Sept. 24, 1964 (Box 5, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0021)
      Original identification number: B-97
    - Alumni Affairs Interview: Mr. Roger Marshall, Nov. 1964 (Box 5, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0022)
      Original identification number: B-106
    - Interview on Food Service: Mr. Ted Minah, Oct. 1, 1964 (Box 5, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0023)
      Original identification number: B-107
    - Writing: Interview with Mr. Reynolds Price, Oct. 2, 1964 (Box 5, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0024)
      Original identification number: B-108
    - Remarks concerning Phytotron: Dr. Paul Kramer, Oct. 1964; 1 sound reel: 5 inch, 1/4 inch. (Box 5, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0025)
      Original identification number: B-110
    - Writing: Interview with Mr. Reynolds Price, Oct. 1964 (Box 5, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0026)
      Original identification number: B-111
    - Oceanography: Interviews, Dr. Robert J. Menzies, Captain Beveridge on Eastward, Nov. 20, 1964 (Box 5, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0027)
      Original identification number: B-129
    - Mr. Wright Tisdale, Chairman of Board of Trustees, speaking at Duke Law School, Nov. 13, 1964 (Box 5, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0028)
      Original identification number: B-133
    - Student Activity: Telephone interview with Mr. Bob Newhart, Oct. 1964 (Box 5, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0029)
      Original identification number: B-140
    - Oceanography: Eastward Sound Effects for the Bridge, Nov. 20, 1964 (Box 5, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0030)
      Original identification number: B-143
    - College Finances: Interview with Mr. C. G. Henricks, Nov. 1964 (Box 5, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0031)
      Original identification number: B-147
    - Miss Heather Low, Pres, Women's Student Government, Feb. 9, 1965 (Box 5, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0032)
      Original identification number: B-190
    - Interview with Dr. Charles Vail on Engineering Week, Feb. 1965 (Box 5, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0033)
      Original identification number: B-201
    - Interview: Mr. Winston Broadfoot on George Washington Flowers Collec., Feb. 22, 1965 (Box 5, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0034)
      Original identification number: B-203
    - The South in Continuity and Change Symposium: Dr. Knight, Dr. Thompson, Feb. 21, 1965 (Box 5, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0035)
      Original identification number: B-216-A
    - The South in Continuity and Change Symposium: Dr. Knight, Dr. Thompson, Feb. 21, 1965 (Box 5, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0036)
      Original identification number: B-216-B
    - Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr.: Student Union Speaker Series, Nov. 1964 (Box 6, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0037)
      Original identification number: B-224-A; Another recording of Dr. King's speech is in the collection: WDBS Collection, 1949-1983. An audiocassette reference copy of this recording has been made; There are two unnumbered tapes in Box 12 of this collection entitled King #1 and King #2. Presumably, these tapes are also recordings of Dr. King's speech
    - Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr.: Student Union Speaker Series, Nov. 1964 (Box 6, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0038)
      Original identification number: B-224-B
    - Dr. Knight's Announcement on the 10 year program, Mar. 9, 1965 (Box 6, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0039)
      Original identification number: B-225
    - Interview: Dr. Kenneth Clark on Greek New Testament Project, Mar. 1965; 0:29:09 (Box 6, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0040, Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0009, Audio-file UA27020001-RR-0040.wav)
      Original identification number: B-234
    - Prof. William Blackburn reading poetry, Apr. 1965 (Box 6, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0041)
      Original identification number: B-242
    - Interview with Prof. Iain Hamilton on composing, Apr. 15, 1965 (Box 6, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0042)
      Original identification number: B-248
    - Student Union Major Speaker: General Lewis B. Hershey, Feb. 13, 1965 (Box 6, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0043)
      Original identification number: B-250
    - Oceanography: Interview with Dr. Robert Menzies, Apr. 21, 1965 (Box 6, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0044)
      Original identification number: B-251
    - Oceanography: Interview with Dr. C. G. Brookhout onboard the "Eastward", Apr. 20, 1965 (Box 6, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0045)
      Original identification number: B-252
    - Vice President Humphrey's Address: Duke University Indoor Stadium, Apr. 24, 1965. (Box 6, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0046)
      Original identification number: B-253-A; A CD reference copy of this recording has been made. Data file masters also exist for this recording.
    - Vice President Humphrey's Address: Duke University Indoor Stadium, Apr. 24, 1965. (Box 6, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0047)
      Original identification number: B-253-B;A CD reference copy of this recording has been made. Data file masters also exist for this recording.
    - Vice President Humphrey's Address: Duke University Indoor Stadium, Copy 2, Apr. 24, 1965. (Box 6, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0048)
      Original identification number: B-253-A
    - Vice President Humphrey's Address: Duke University Indoor Stadium, Copy 2, Apr. 24, 1965. (Box 6, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0049)
      Original identification number: B-253-B
    - Oceanography: Eastward Dedication Luncheon, Morehead City, N.C., May 1, 1965 (Box 6, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0050)
      Original identification number: B-260
    - Oceanography: Eastward Dedication Dock Ceremonies, May 1, 1965 (Box 6, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0051)
      Original identification number: B-261-A
    - Oceanography: Eastward Dedication Dock Ceremonies, May 1, 1965 (Box 6, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0052)
      Original identification number: B-261-B
    - Interview: Dr. Marcus E. Hobbs on the Research Triangle Institute, undated (Box 6, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0053)
      Original identification number: B-263
    - Education: Interview with Miss Fannie Mitchell on Job Placement, May 25, 1965 (Box 6, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0054)
      Original identification number: B-273
    - Study of American States: Interview: Former N.C. Governor Terry Sanford, Quail Roost, Mar. 28, 1965 (Box 6, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0055)
      Original identification number: B-274
    - Graduation Exercises: Gr. Gordon N. Ray, Pres. John Simon Gughenheim Fndtn.: "The Arts and Humanities", June 7, 1965 (Box 6, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0056)
      Original identification number: B-281
    - Dr. Douglas Knight: Address at UNC Commencement, June 7, 1965 (Box 6, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0057)
      Original identification number: B-282
    - Interview with Mr. Anton Brees, Carillon Recital, June 6, 1965 (Box 6, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0058)
      Original identification number: B-286
    - Duke Chapel Carillon Feature for WPTF Kaleidoscope: Mr. Anton Brees, June 1965 (Box 6, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0059)
      Original identification number: B-301
    - Economics: Interview with Dr. Calvin Hoover, June 1965 (Box 6, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0060)
      Original identification number: B-302-A
    - Parapsychology: Interview with Dr. J. B. Rhine, Aug. 1965 (Box 6, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0061)
      Original identification number: B-323
    - Duke Chapel Carillon, Aug. 7, 1965 (Box 6, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0062)
      Original identification number: B-324
    - Interview with Dean E. R. Latty, Sept. 13, 1965 (Box 6, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0063)
      Original identification number: B-331
    - Duke Convocation: Dr. D. M. Knight, Mr. G. Allen, Sept. 23, 1965 (Box 6, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0064)
      Original identification number: B-339
    - Library Ground-breaking, Sept. 23, 1965 (Box 6, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0065)
      Original identification number: B-340
    - Interview and sound effects: Mr. Giorgio Ciompi on the violin, Oct. 1, 1965 (Box 6, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0066)
      Original identification number: B-344
    - Sound effects: Duke Chapel Carillon, Chapel Organ, Classroom sounds, undated (Box 6, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0067)
      Original identification number: B-349
    - Interview: Dean Margaret Ball on Education and Women, Oct. 26, 1965 (Box 6, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0068)
      Original identification number: B-356
    - Dr. Knight's Speech to Erasmus Club: The Longest Journey, Nov. 1, 1965 (Box 6, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0069)
      Original identification number: B-360
    - Congressman C. Weltner's Speech at Duke Law School, Nov. 8, 1965; 1 sound reel: 5 inch, 1/4 inch. (Box 6, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0070)
      Original identification number: B-364
    - Reverend Read: Who's God is Dead, Nov. 14, 1965 (Box 6, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0071)
      Original identification number: B-371
    - Interview: Dr. Henry Newson on the Van de Graph [Van de Graaff] Accelerator, Dec. 1965 (Box 6, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0072)
      Original identification number: B-374
    - Physics: Press Conference on Nuclear Structure Lab, Nov. 23, 1965 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0073)
      Original identification number: B-377
    - Narration from Duke Univ. Movie, Response to our Challenge, Dec. 1965 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0074)
      Original identification number: B-379
    - Dr. Thomas J. J. Altizer Speech in Duke Chapel, God is Dead, Nov. 9, 1965 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0075)
      Original identification number: B-385
    - International Rule of Law in Propaganda Conference, Feb. 18, 1966 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0076)
      Original identification number: B-431-A
    - International Rule of Law in Propaganda Conference, Feb. 18, 1966 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0077)
      Original identification number: B-431-B
    - Discussion at International Rule of Law in Propaganda Conference, Feb. 22, 1966 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0078)
      Original identification number: B-431-C
    - Interview: Dr. Arthur Larson on Propaganda Conference, Feb. 22, 1966 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0079)
      Original identification number: B-432
    - Interview: Dr. Thomas Gallie on the Research Triangle Computer Center, Feb. 22, 1966 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0080)
      Original identification number: B-433
    - Research Triangle Computer Center Opening, Feb. 14, 1966; 1 sound reel: 5 inch, 1/4 inch. (Box 7, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0081)
      Original identification number: B-434
    - Oceanography: Interview: Dr. C. G. Brookhout on the expansion of the Duke Marine Lab, Mar. 2, 1966 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0082)
      Original identification number: B-437
    - Oceanography: Interview: Dr. Robert Menzies on the Peru Expedition, Mar. 3, 1966 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0083)
      Original identification number: B-441-A
    - Oceanography: Interview: Dr. Robert Menzies on the Peru Expedition, Mar. 3, 1966 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0084)
      Original identification number: B-441-B
    - Interview with Mr. Reynolds Price on writing for WPTF, Mar. 7, 1966 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0085)
      Original identification number: B-442
    - Dr. Herbert Aptheker Speech in Page Auditorium, Mar. 8, 1966 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0086)
      Original identification number: B-446
    - Dr. Herbert Aptheker Question and Answer Period, Mar. 8, 1966 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0087)
      Original identification number: B-447
    - Speech by Mr. Malcolm Cowley on The Genius and Talent of William Faulkner, March 16, 1966 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0088)
      Original identification number: B-471
    - Interview: Reynolds Price on "A Generous Man" for WPTF Radio, Mar. 38 [sic]; 1966 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0089)
      Original identification number: B-477
    - National Fencing Championships: Two Interviews with John LeBar for WPTF, Mar. 1966 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0090)
      Original identification number: B-481
    - Selected Sculpture and Decorative Art: Brummer Collection, May 6, 1967 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0091)
      Original identification number: B-482-A
    - Selected Sculpture and Decorative Art: Brummer Collection, May 6, 1967 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0092)
      Original identification number: B-482-B
    - Dr. Douglas Knight at Newcomen Society Dinner, Apr. 18, 1966 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0093)
      Original identification number: B-487
    - Oceanography: Interview: Dr. B. C. Heezen on his oceanographic discovery on Eastward, Mar. 30, 1966 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0094)
      Original identification number: B-490
    - Richard Nixon: Press Conference Duke University Law Day, Apr. 30, 1966 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0095)
      Original identification number: B-494; A CD reference copy of this recording has been made. Data file masters also exist for this recording.
    - Dr. Arthur A. Lawson: Student sponsored speech on Viet Nam, Apr. 19, 1966 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0096)
      Original identification number: B-497-A
    - Oceanography: Two interviews: Dr. Orin Pilkey, Mr. George Newton, May 6, 1966; 1 sound reel: 5 inch, 1/4 inch. (Box 7, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0097)
      Original identification number: B-503
    - Dean Miller's Address: 30th Reunion, Jan. 29, 1966; 1 sound reel: 5 inch, 1/4 inch. (Box 7, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0098)
      Original identification number: B-504
    - Annual Meeting Law School Alumni Assoc., Apr. 30, 1966 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0099)
      Original identification number: B-505
    - Oceanography: Interviews with Dr. Orin Pilkey and George Newton, May 1966 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0100)
      Original identification number: B-507
    - Sound effect of a frog, Duke Gardens, May 1966 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0101)
      Original identification number: B-509
    - Lecture given by Chief Justice Charles S. Desmond, May 13, 1966 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0102)
      Original identification number: B-510-A
    - Interview: Mr. A. Loy Nash on Barber Writes a Book for Margaret Brickell WPTF, May 17, 1966 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0103)
      Original identification number: B-516
    - Commencement: Interview with James F. Webb, Dr. Townes, June 6, 1966 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0104)
      Original identification number: B-519
    - Report to Board of Trustees by Dr. Douglas M. Knight, June 1966; 1 sound reel: 5 inch, 1/4 inch. (Box 7, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0105)
      Original identification number: B-522
    - Alumni Lecture Series: Mr. Joe Tally, Dr. Theodore Ropp, June 4, 1966 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0106)
      Original identification number: B-524-A
    - Alumni Lecture Series: Dr. Calvin Hoover and Question Period, June 4, 1966 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0107)
      Original identification number: B-524-B
    - Graduation Exercises: Address by Dr. Charles H. Townes, June 1966 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0108)
      Original identification number: B-525
    - Dean Robert Cushman's comments on The Vatican Council, June 1966 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0109)
      Original identification number: B-527
    - Interview: Dean Robert Cushman on II Vatican Council, June 21, 1966 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0110)
      Original identification number: B-531
    - Interview with Dr. E. R. Latty on Trends and Changes in Law, Sept. 1966 (Box 8, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0148)
      Original identification number: B-569
    - Speech by Bishop Pike, Oct. 11, 1966 (Box 8, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0149)
      Original identification number: B-582-A
    - Speech by Bishop Pike, Oct. 11, 1966 (Box 8, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0150)
      Original identification number: B-582-B
    - News Conference with Bishop Pike, Oct. 10, 1966 (Box 8, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0151)
      Original identification number: B-583
    - Dr. Walter Nielsen: Retirement Dinner in his honor, Oct. 7, 1966 (Box 8, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0152)
      Original identification number: B-584
    - National Academy of Sciences Dinner/Address by Dr. Knight, Oct. 18, 1966 (Box 8, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0153)
      Original identification number: B-590
    - National Academy of Science Major Address by Dr. Weinburg, Oct. 17, 1966 (Box 8, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0154)
      Original identification number: B-600-A
    - National Academy of Science Major Address by Dr. Weinburg, Oct. 17, 1966 (Box 8, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0155)
      Original identification number: B-600-B
    - Ceremony to name the Duke University Library The William R. Perkins Library, Dec. 11, 1966 (Box 8, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0156)
      Original identification number: B-602
    - Durham welcomes Dr. Douglas M. Knight, Sept. 19, 1963 (Box 8, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0157)
      Original identification number: B-603
    - Campus Club Meeting, Feb. 8, 1967 (Box 8, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0158)
      Original identification number: B-606
    - Student Union Major Speaker: Justice Byron R. White, Mar. 6, 1967 (Box 8, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0159)
      Original identification number: B-607
    - Student Union Major Speaker: Mr. Stokely Carmichael, Apr. 1967 (Box 8, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0160)
      Original identification number: B-608-A
    - Student Union Major Speaker: Mr. Stokely Carmichael, Apr. 1967 (Box 8, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0161)
      Original identification number: B-608-B
    - Student Union: Mr. Christopher Craft, May 9, 1967 (Box 8, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0162)
      Original identification number: B-609-A
    - Student Union: Mr. Christopher Craft, May 9, 1967 (Box 8, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0163)
      Original identification number: B-609-B
    - Remarks by Dr. Knight to Board of Trustees, Mar. 4, 1967-Mar. 5, 1967 (Box 8, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0164)
      Original identification number: B-613
    - President Knight's speech to Executive Committee, Sept. 25, 1964 (Box 8, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0165)
      Original identification number: B-614
    - Interview with Dr. Kenneth Clark on the International Greek New Testament Project, July 1967 (Box 8, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0166)
      Original identification number: B-616-A
    - Interview with Dr. Kenneth Clark on the International Greek New Testament Project, July 1967 (Box 8, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0167)
      Original identification number: B-616-B
    - Special Report fed to CBS by John Van Hecke: Dr. Knight's comments on the public housing in Durham, N.C., July 27, 1967 (Box 8, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0168)
      Original identification number: B-617
    - Dedication of Wallace Wade Stadium, July 27, 1967 (Box 8, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0169)
      Original identification number: B-618
    - News Conference: Dr. Knight's comments to the news media concerning the public housing situation in Durham, N. C., July 27, 1967 (Box 8, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0170)
      Original identification number: B-619
    - North Carolina News Conference: Guest Speaker Dr. Douglas Knight, July 31, 1967 (Box 8, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0171)
      Original identification number: B-620
    - Dr. Knight: Meeting of the Board of Trustees Evening Session, Nov. 1964 (Box 8, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0172)
      Original identification number: B-621-A
    - Dr. Knight: Meeting of the Board of Trustees Evening Session, Nov. 1964 (Box 8, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0173)
      Original identification number: B-621-B
    - Dr. Knight's Report to the Board of Trustees, June 3, 1967 (Box 8, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0174)
      Original identification number: B-626
    - Duke University Convocation, Provost Taylor Cole presiding, Sept. 20, 1967 (Box 8, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0175)
      Original identification number: B-629-A
    - Duke University Convocation, Sept. 29, 1967 (Box 8, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0176)
      Original identification number: B-629-B
    - Phone interviews with Howard, Tipton, Wilkinson, Prothro, all paying tribute to Coach Wallace Wade, Oct. 1967 (Box 8, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0177)
      Original identification number: B-630
    - Student Union Major Speaker: Norman Cousins, Oct. 12, 1967 (Box 8, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0178)
      Original identification number: B-631
    - Mr. George V. Allen's speech to the Tobaccoland Kiwanis Club, Dec. 1967 (Box 8, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0179)
      Original identification number: B-632
    - Dr. Douglas Knight's speech to the Tobaccoland Kiwanis Club, Jan. 8, 1968 (Box 8, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0180)
      Original identification number: B-633
    - Student Union Major Speaker: Mr. Gerald Ford speaking in U. S. Economic Policy, Feb. 2, 1968 (Box 8, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0181)
      Original identification number: B-634
    - Dr. Knight's Report to the Faculty, Mar. 21, 1968 (Box 8, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0182)
      Original identification number: B-635
    - Student Union Major Speaker: Dr. Sidney Cohen speaking on LSD, Mar. 18, 1968 (Box 8, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0183)
      Original identification number: B-637-A
    - Student Union Major Speaker: Dr. Sidney Cohen speaking on LSD, Mar. 18, 1968 (Box 9, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0184)
      Original identification number: B-637-B
    - Duke University Service for Peace in Duke Chapel, Apr. 3, 1968 (Box 9, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0185)
      Original identification number: B-638
    - Student Union Major Speaker: Dr. Adam Clayton Powell, Apr. 1, 1968 (Box 9, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0186)
      Original identification number: B-639-A
    - Mr. Charles B. Wade, Jr.: Who Will be the Next Mr. Duke?, Dec. 10, 1967 (Box 9, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0187)
      Original identification number: B-640
    - Oceanography: Interview on Board the Eastward, Nov. 1967 (Box 9, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0188)
      Original identification number: B-641
    - Memorial Service at Duke Chapel for Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr., Apr. 6, 1968 (Box 9, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0189)
      Original identification number: B-643-A